stampington.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - Stampington & Company

##  **Stampington & Company and Stampington.com Privacy Policy**

This is the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") of Stampington & Company LLC and the website located at [stampington.com](https://stampington.com/) (sometimes referred to as the "Site"). We want you to understand the types of information we gather about you, how we use it, and the steps we take to safeguard it. Throughout this policy, "Stampington & Company," "We," "Our," and "Us" means Stampington & Company LLC.

This policy applies to information collected from you at the Site. It also applies to information that We may collect from you elsewhere or by other means (for example, if you contact our customer service and/or ordering departments by mail or telephone), unless We inform you otherwise. When you provide Personal Information at the Site or by other means, you are consenting to the manner in which We will collect, store, use, and disclose that information as set forth below.

[How You Can Access, Correct, and Amend Your Personal Information](https://stampington.com/privacy-policy#3)  

**The Way We Use Information**  
Your privacy is important to us. Stampington & Company does not sell, trade, or rent your personal or contact information to other marketers. This has been our unwavering operating policy since 1994.

You are not required to provide any Personal Information in order to have general access to the Site. However, in order to make purchases, to access certain information, features, or services at the Site or offerings of Stampington & Company, you may be required to provide certain Personal Information. We collect Personal Information about you from the following sources:

  * When you shop with Stampington & Company, including at Stampington.com, We obtain from you the information that We need to process and complete your transaction, which includes the following Personal Information: 
    1. First and Last Name
    2. Mailing Address
    3. Email Address
    4. Telephone Number
    5. Social Security Number _(if applicable)_

  * When you establish an account or register to use certain features at the Site.
  * If you provide us with comments or suggestions, request information about our products and services, or contact our customer service or order department via phone, email, or other forms of communication.
  * We may collect additional information if you choose to use or participate in one of our various services, programs, or surveys. For example, if you sign up for our wish list service, We will ask you for information concerning your gift selections.
  * From time to time we may run promotions or contests, and collect Personal Information from you if you participate in them.
  * We obtain information concerning the specific products or services you purchase or use from your transactions and other interactions with Us.

"Personal Information" is information that may be used, either alone or in combination with other information, to identify you.

**Email Communications**  

You may be contacted via email by Stampington & Company regarding your order, your account, or certain other matters. Typically, we send two types of email communications. You may receive transactional emails that provide you withinformation about your order, such as order acknowledgements and confirmations, order numbers, access to the status of your order, notification of shipment and other related information, or notifications concerning our business relationship. Since we need to communicate this information to you, you will not be able to opt out of such transactional emails.

In addition to the transactional emails described above, you also may receive certain marketing email communications, including content and newsletters you have signed up for. You can change your mind at any time by clicking the Unsubscribe link in the footer of any non-operational email you receive. 

You will also be able to manage your preferences or choose which type of emails you would like to receive at the bottom of any marketing-related email. Please send an email to [marketing@stampington.com](mailto:marketing@stampington.com) if you need assistance.  

**How You Can Access, Correct, and Amend Your Personal Information**  
Stampington & Company provides you access to your account at Stampington.com. In order to view your account information, please click the "[Login](https://stampington.com/index.php?route=account/login)" link at the top of the home page. From this link, you can view and change some of the Personal Information that We have collected from you (such as email address, mailing address, wish list, and address book).

**How We Use Cookies — Do Not Track Signals**  
We keep track of individual visitors to our Site through the use of "cookies" and other web technologies, which are individually or collectively referred to herein as "Tracking Technologies." Cookies are small files that contain a short line of text. They contain absolutely no personally identifiable information about you. These text files are sent to your Internet browser which, in turn, places information from the text file in its cookie file (you can view this file in your Internet browser). Cookies identify you as you move from page to page and allow Us to collect information to keep track of your visit. For example, cookies allow Us to know what item(s) you have placed in your shopping cart, and cookies keep that information for checkout even if you decide to leave the Site and return at a later time to finish shopping.

We use Tracking Technologies to improve your navigation and user-experience across our website, and they may also be used to select banner and other advertising that is better tailored to your interests. For these reasons, it is essential that, in order for you to order from our Site, you enable the "accept cookies" option on your browser. We hope this explanation will allay any concerns you may have about how our Site operates. The use of Tracking Technologies is standard on the Internet and is used to make online shopping easier and quicker. You may, of course, choose not to accept cookies. However, if you choose not to accept cookies, purchasing is not possible from the Stampington.com Site. If you do not accept cookies, you may still place your order by calling our customer service number at 877-782-6737.

**Aggregate Information**  
We collect non-personally identifiable information about how users navigate to and through the Site, including the number of visits to the Site and specific pages visited while at the Site and the IP addresses of those visitors to the Site. We aggregate this statistical information and use it to help us administer and to enhance the Site and for research and development, user analysis, and business decision making. These aggregate statistics also may be provided to Third Parties to assist us with our marketing and advertising activities and/or to assist service providers in connection with the taking or processing of orders, as well as maintaining operation of the Site.

**Do We Disclose Any Information To Outside Parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties, your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or other's rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third Party Links**  
Occasionally, and at our discretion, We may include or offer Third party products or services on our website. These Third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, We seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because We value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your Personal Information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the "Edit Account" page.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of [COPPA](http://www.coppa.org/coppa.htm) (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years of age or older. Stampington & Company does not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13. We also do not knowingly post content provided by minors such as reviews, comments, or blog posts. If you believe we might have any information or content from a child under the age of 13, please contact us by telephone at 877-782-6737 or email us at [retail@stampington.com](mailto:retail@stampington.com).

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your Personal Information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your Personal Information. When you use a credit or debit card, or other forms of online payment to make a purchase at Stampington.com, We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

If you would prefer to use the phone, please call our customer service number at 877-782-6737, and one of Our customer service associates will gladly assist you with your order.

**Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information**  
We maintain security practices designed to protect the security, integrity, and confidentiality of customer information. We restrict access to your Personal Information to those employees who need access to that information to provide products or services to you. Our servers are located in the United States, and We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your Personal Information.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to amend this policy from time to time and to apply any changes to information previously collected as permitted by law. If we amend our Privacy Policy in any material way, we will post those changes on the Site. (Changes in contact information or minor typographical errors will simply be corrected on the Site.) Please check back periodically to view this Privacy Policy as you continue to use our Site.

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

**This policy was last modified on 3/11/2014.**

**Contacting Us**  
If you have a comment or question about this privacy policy, please send us an email to [retail@stampington.com](mailto:retail@stampington.com) or write us:

**Stampington & Company **  
**Attn: Customer Service Department**  
22992 Mill Creek Drive  
Laguna Hills, CA 92653  
(949) 380-7318 • Fax (949) 380-9355  
Toll free (877) STAMPER (782-6737)

©1999–2014 Stampington & Company LLC. All Rights Reserved.
